[newscaster] The collapse of the Mapo Citizens' Apartment
[مذيع إخباري] انهيار شقة مواطني مابو
already notorious for shoddy construction…
مشهورة بالفعل بالبناء الرديء…
[man] Would you look at that? The world has gone crazy.
[رجل] هل تنظر إلى ذلك؟ لقد أصبح العالم مجنونا.
It's not long before everything goes to hell.
لن يمر وقت طويل قبل أن يذهب كل شيء إلى الجحيم.
Well, I guess it had a good run.
حسنًا، أعتقد أنها كانت مسيرة جيدة.
One day, the whole world will come crashing down like that apartment.
في يوم من الأيام، سوف ينهار العالم كله مثل تلك الشقة.
Will you stop with the doom and gloom already?
هل ستتوقف عن العذاب والكآبة بالفعل؟
What about our Huijeong? Want her to die before she even blooms?
ماذا عن Huijeong لدينا؟ هل تريدها أن تموت قبل أن تزهر؟
I'm just saying. The world is not going to fold that easily.
أنا فقط أقول. العالم لن يطوي بهذه السهولة.
The doenjang stew is good.
حساء دوينجانج جيد.
I'm scared the baby might hear you.
أخشى أن الطفل قد يسمعك.
With its so-called dad spouting that kind of talk,
مع ما يسمى بأبي ينشر هذا النوع من الحديث،
you think it'd even want to be born?
هل تعتقد أنه يريد حتى أن يولد؟
Geez. I'm sorry, okay? Let's just eat.
الجيز. أنا آسف، حسنا؟ دعونا نأكل فقط.
[newscaster continues]
[يواصل المذيع]
[banging on door]
[خبط على الباب]
[man] Who's that?
[رجل] من هذا؟
[banging on door continues]
[يستمر الطرق على الباب]
[man] Damn, who is it?
[رجل] اللعنة، من هو؟
[Robert speaking in English] Mr. Kim, it… It's Robert.
[روبرت يتحدث باللغة الإنجليزية] السيد كيم، إنه... إنه روبرت.
[in English] Are you nuts?
[باللغة الإنجليزية] هل أنت مجنون؟
I told you not to come to my house.
قلت لك ألا تأتي إلى منزلي.
[Robert] Mr. Kim, we're going back to the States next week.
[روبرت] سيد كيم، سنعود إلى الولايات المتحدة الأسبوع المقبل.
For old times' sake, let me have it just this once.
من أجل الزمن القديم، دعني أحصل عليه هذه المرة فقط.
I'll pay you double.
سأدفع لك ضعف.
Double?
مزدوج؟
[in Korean] Damn it.
[باللغة الكورية] اللعنة.
[in English] Come on.
[باللغة الإنجليزية] هيا.
[in Korean] Have you lost it? What were you thinking calling them here?
[باللغة الكورية] هل فقدته؟ ماذا كنت تفكر في دعوتهم هنا؟
I didn't. They showed up on their own.
لم أكن. لقد ظهروا من تلقاء أنفسهم.
[phone ringing]
[رنين الهاتف]
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
BEOMCHEON-DONG, CAFÉ C'EST…
بيومتشون دونغ، القهوة هي...
Got it. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
فهمتها. سوف أراك غدا. الوداع.
[whispering] They said they'll pay double.
[همس] قالوا أنهم سيدفعون الضعف.
Let's just give it and send them away. Go get it.
دعونا فقط نعطيها ونرسلهم بعيدا. اذهب واحصل عليه.
Hurry, go grab it.
على عجل، اذهب الاستيلاء عليه.
-[clamoring] -[man] What? Have you lost your mind?
-[صراخ] -[رجل] ماذا؟ هل فقدت عقلك؟
-[woman] What the hell are you doing? -[violent thrashing]
-[امرأة] ماذا تفعلين بحق الجحيم؟ -[الضرب العنيف]
-[♪ dark music] -[Robert shouting irately]
-[♪ موسيقى داكنة] -[روبرت يصرخ بغضب]
-[stabbing] -[clattering, crashing]
-[طعن] -[قعقعة، تحطم]
[woman screaming]
[صراخ امرأة]
[dramatic sting]
[لدغة درامية]
-[♪ moody jazz music] -[siren wailing]
-[♪ موسيقى جاز متقلبة المزاج] -[صافرة الإنذار]
[man gagging, retches]
[رجل يتقيأ، يتقيأ]
[coughing]
[السعال]
[chattering]
[الثرثرة]
[investigator] Huh? Mr. Jang.
[المحقق] هاه؟ السيد جانج.
Be careful.
احرص.
[sighs softly]
[تنهد بهدوء]
[girl fussing softly]
[فتاة تداعب بهدوء]
[Investigator Kim] Evening, sir. [clears throat]
[المحقق كيم] مساء الخير يا سيدي. [يمسح الحلق]
The victims were married.
الضحايا كانوا متزوجين.
Kim Taeyeong, 29 years old, and his wife, Lee Suni, 26.
كيم تايونغ، 29 عامًا، وزوجته لي سوني، 26 عامًا.
They had a three-year-old daughter, and…
وكان لديهما ابنة تبلغ من العمر ثلاث سنوات،…
the wife was pregnant.
وكانت الزوجة حامل.
[clears throat] Oh, and this.
[يمسح الحلق] أوه، وهذا.
The US Army already took them into custody and got their confessions.
وقد قام الجيش الأمريكي باحتجازهم بالفعل وحصل على اعترافاتهم.
First,
أولاً،
let's get the kid out of here.
دعنا نخرج الطفل من هنا
She doesn't really have anywhere else to go.
ليس لديها حقًا أي مكان آخر تذهب إليه.
Her uncle's on his way now.
عمها في طريقه الآن.
[sighs] Is it because of the rain?
[تنهد] هل هو بسبب المطر؟
The whole place reeks of blood.
المكان كله تفوح منه رائحة الدم.
[grunts, sighs]
[الهمهمات، تنهدات]
[door opens]
[يفتح الباب]
-[♪ intriguing music plays] -[door closes]
-[♪ تشغيل موسيقى مثيرة] -[يُغلق الباب]
BEOMCHEON-DONG, CAFÉ C'EST LA VIE, 6 P.M., 1 KG
بيومتشيون دونغ، القهوة هي الحياة، 6 مساءً، 1 كجم
[girl fussing softly]
[فتاة تداعب بهدوء]
[giggling]
[يضحك]
[Geonyoung] This child's parents were drug dealers.
[Geonyoung] كان والدا هذا الطفل من تجار المخدرات.
Middlemen who got meth from suppliers and sold it on to end consumers.
الوسطاء الذين حصلوا على الميثامفيتامين من الموردين وباعوه للمستهلكين النهائيين.
[siren wailing in distance]
[صافرة الإنذار تبكي من مسافة]
The couple seemed as ordinary as anyone,
بدا الزوجان عاديين مثل أي شخص آخر،
but they were murdered by US soldiers while dealing drugs.
لكنهما قُتلا على يد جنود أمريكيين أثناء تعاطيهما للمخدرات.
Those US soldiers were addicted to meth.
كان هؤلاء الجنود الأمريكيون مدمنين على الميثامفيتامين.
They never had the money to buy it in the first place.
لم يكن لديهم المال لشرائه في المقام الأول.
With no money, they had to steal.
ومع عدم وجود المال، كان عليهم أن يسرقوا.
Once you're hooked on meth…
بمجرد أن تصبح مدمن مخدرات على الميثامفيتامين ...
-Move, please! -…nothing else matters.
- تحرك من فضلك! -…لا شىئ اخر يهم.
This way, sir.
بهذه الطريقة يا سيدي.
[Geonyoung] I bet that's what happened when they killed this girl's parents.
[Geonyoung] أراهن أن هذا ما حدث عندما قتلوا والدي هذه الفتاة.
They decided their own craving mattered more than someone else's life.
لقد قرروا أن شغفهم الخاص أهم من حياة شخص آخر.
This girl's name is Kim Huijeong.
اسم هذه الفتاة هو كيم Huijeong.
Now that her parents are dead,
والآن بعد أن مات والداها،
the bottle in her mouth is all she has to survive on.
الزجاجة التي في فمها هي كل ما لديها لتعيش عليه.
When she grows up, will she remember this moment?
عندما تكبر، هل ستتذكر هذه اللحظة؟
People say time heals all wounds.
يقول الناس أن الوقت يشفي كل الجروح.
That everything gets better with time.
أن كل شيء يتحسن مع مرور الوقت.
But this girl will remember this for the rest of her life.
لكن هذه الفتاة سوف تتذكر هذا لبقية حياتها.
Her own face as she sucked on the bottle,
وجهها وهي تمص الزجاجة،
her parents' faces as their throats were cut over a drug deal,
وجوه والديها عندما تم قطع حناجرهما بسبب صفقة مخدرات،
and the stench of blood that filled the room.
ورائحة الدم التي ملأت الغرفة.
If there really is a God,
إذا كان هناك إله حقاً،
may he save this girl's soul
لعله ينقذ روح هذه الفتاة
from the power of the dog.
من قوة الكلب.
[♪ relentlessly frenetic music plays]
[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى المحمومة بلا هوادة]
[Geonyoung humming]
[همهمة جيونيونج]
Ah, ah. [clears throat]
اه اه. [يمسح الحلق]
[Geonyoung resumes humming]
[تستأنف جيونيونج الطنين]
[Geonyoung clears his throat]
[جيونيونج نظف حلقه]
[investigators] Good afternoon, sir.
[المحققون] مساء الخير يا سيدي.
[man] What's that?
[رجل] ما هذا؟
Well, I went home to grab some files I'd forgotten.
حسنًا، لقد عدت إلى المنزل لأحضر بعض الملفات التي نسيتها.
-[man] On your bike? -[Geonyoung] Yes.
-[رجل] على دراجتك؟ -[جيونيونج] نعم.
Did you guys eat yet?
هل تناولتم الطعام يا رفاق بعد؟
[investigators] Yes.
[المحققون] نعم.
[Investigator Kim] Sure did.
[المحقق كيم] بالتأكيد فعل ذلك.
[Geonyoung] Can you order me a jjajangmyeon? Make it extra-large.
[Geonyoung] هل يمكنك أن تطلب لي jjajangmyeon؟ اجعلها كبيرة جدًا.
-[investigator] Yes, sir. -[man] Hey, Jang!
-[المحقق] نعم يا سيدي. -[رجل] مرحبًا، جانج!
Listen.
يستمع.
You said you weren't taking public security cases.
لقد قلت أنك لن تتولى قضايا الأمن العام.
[Geonyoung] That's right.
[جيونيونج] هذا صحيح.
Then focus on narcotics.
ثم التركيز على المخدرات.
Why are you poking around in a public security case?
لماذا تتجول في قضية الأمن العام؟
[Geonyoung] It's connected to the victims in my case, so I looked into it.
[Geonyoung] إنه مرتبط بالضحايا في حالتي، لذلك نظرت في الأمر.
Being a KCIA informant doesn't mean you can't be a junkie too, right?
كونك مخبرًا لـ KCIA لا يعني أنك لا تستطيع أن تكون مدمنًا أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
Jang.
جانج.
When I first met you at the Seoul Office,
عندما التقيت بك لأول مرة في مكتب سيول،
I was a section chief, and you were just a prosecutor with no title, right?
لقد كنت رئيس قسم، وكنت مجرد مدعي عام بدون لقب، أليس كذلك؟
And when I was in Gwangju as a departmental chief,
وعندما كنت في غوانغجو كرئيس قسم،
you still had no title.
لا يزال ليس لديك عنوان.
And now, I've been sent here to Busan as the deputy chief prosecutor.
والآن، تم إرسالي إلى هنا إلى بوسان بصفتي نائب رئيس النيابة.
But you? You're still without a title.
لكن أنت؟ أنت لا تزال بدون عنوان.
All your peers are section chiefs now, some moving up to departmental chiefs.
أصبح جميع زملائك الآن رؤساء أقسام، وبعضهم ينتقل إلى رؤساء أقسام.
How long will you keep drifting around the country without a title?
إلى متى ستستمر في التجوال في جميع أنحاء البلاد دون لقب؟
[Geonyoung] Well, all I can do is give it my best.
[Geonyoung] حسنًا، كل ما يمكنني فعله هو أن أبذل قصارى جهدي.
[chief prosecutor] That's exactly why you never get promoted. You're too rigid.
[رئيس النيابة] هذا هو بالضبط سبب عدم حصولك على ترقية. أنت جامد جدًا.
No flexibility!
لا مرونة!
Learn to work the hierarchy.
تعلم كيفية العمل بالتسلسل الهرمي.
What do you think an organization is, huh?
ما رأيك في المنظمة، هاه؟
[Geonyoung] An organization is a place where you work.
[Geonyoung] المنظمة هي المكان الذي تعمل فيه.
I still have work to do, so I'd better get to it now.
لا يزال لدي عمل لأقوم به، لذا من الأفضل أن أقوم به الآن.
Jang. Don't mess with the KCIA, all right?
جانج. لا تعبث مع KCIA، حسنًا؟
Cross them and we're the only ones who bleed.
اعبرهم ونحن الوحيدون الذين ننزف.
[Geonyoung] Okay. I'll keep that in mind and do my best, sir.
[جيونيونج] حسنًا. سأضع ذلك في الاعتبار وأبذل قصارى جهدي يا سيدي.
We certainly can't have bloodshed on the job. [sighs]
بالتأكيد لا يمكننا إراقة الدماء أثناء العمل. [تنهدات]
[chief prosecutor] You're impossible.
[رئيس النيابة] أنت مستحيل.
Open a window in here, will you? It smells like…
افتح نافذة هنا، هل ستفعل؟ رائحتها مثل…
And turn the lights on! It's so dark in here.
وأشعل الأضواء! الجو مظلم جدًا هنا.
-Yes, sir. -What is this, a rat's nest?
-نعم يا سيدي. -ما هذا، عش الفئران؟
-[scattered coughing] -Geez.
-[سعال متقطع] -يا إلهي.
Well, I'm off!
حسنا، أنا خارج!
[investigators] Good day, sir!
[المحققون] يوم جيد يا سيدي!
-[Geonyoung] Turn them off. -[door slams shut]
-[Geonyoung] أطفئهم. -[يُغلق الباب]
The lights.
الأضواء.
Goodness.
الخير.
It's nice and gloomy, isn't it?
إنه لطيف وكئيب، أليس كذلك؟
[laughing]
[يضحك]
-You order my jjajangmyeon yet? -[investigator] Yes, sir.
-هل طلبت jjajangmyeon الخاص بي حتى الآن؟ -[المحقق] نعم يا سيدي.
[♪ graceful piano music playing]
[♪ عزف موسيقى البيانو الرائعة]
DIRECTOR GENERAL HWANG GUKPYEONG
المدير العام هوانج جوكبيونج
[Kitae] Director General Hwang Gukpyeong, my direct superior.
[كيتاي] المدير العام هوانج جوكبيونج، رئيسي المباشر.
In charge of the entire Busan branch of the KCIA.
المسؤول عن فرع بوسان بأكمله لـ KCIA.
[Kitae] It got on me.
[كيتاي] لقد أصابني ذلك.
One word from him, and the whole city moves.
كلمة واحدة منه، وتتحرك المدينة كلها.
[Gukpyeong] Anyway,
[غوكبيونغ] على أية حال،
about Jo Manjae.
عن جو مانجاي.
I hear he's been dealing meth with the Yakuza.
سمعت أنه كان يتاجر بالميثامفيتامين مع الياكوزا.
Yes, I'm aware.
نعم، أنا على علم.
You're aware?
هل أنت على علم؟
[Kitae] Yes, sir.
[كيتاي] نعم يا سيدي.
[Kitae] That meth is what I loaded onto the plane and sent off to Pyongyang.
[كيتاي] هذا الميثامفيتامين هو ما حملته على متن الطائرة وأرسلته إلى بيونغ يانغ.
The Manjae Gang's meth.
ميث عصابة مانجاي.
[♪ stirring jazz music plays]
[♪ تشغيل موسيقى الجاز المثيرة]
[Kitae] The Manjae Gang, Busan's biggest crime syndicate.
[كيتاي] عصابة مانجاي، أكبر عصابة إجرامية في بوسان.
KANG DAEIL, THE MANJAE GANG UNDERBOSS
كانغ دايل، رئيس عصابة مانجاي
JO MANJAE, THE MANJAE GANG BOSS
جو مانجاي، رئيس عصابة مانجاي
Under Director Hwang's protection, they grew fast.
وتحت حماية المدير هوانج، نمت بسرعة.
They kick back 30% of their monthly take to him,
إنهم يعيدون له 30% من دخلهم الشهري،
straight into the KCIA's pocket.
مباشرة في جيب KCIA.
The gang pulls every crime in the book
العصابة تسحب كل جريمة في الكتاب
and rakes in a million dollars from the underworld.
ويحصل على مليون دولار من العالم السفلي.
At this point, you could say they practically run the Busan economy.
في هذه المرحلة، يمكنك القول إنهم يديرون اقتصاد بوسان عمليًا.
[both chuckling]
[كلاهما يضحك]
EPISODE 2: THE POWER OF THE DOG
الحلقة 2: قوة الكلب
-[♪ graceful piano music plays] -I was planning to take care of it myself.
-[♪ عزف موسيقى بيانو رائعة] - كنت أخطط للاهتمام بها بنفسي.
Jang Geonyoung, a prosecutor at the Busan District Prosecutors' Office,
جانج جيون يونج، المدعي العام في مكتب المدعي العام لمنطقة بوسان،
is apparently gunning for Jo Manjae, all fired up.
يبدو أنه يطلق النار على جو مانجاي، وكلهم متحمسون.
They say he's a Marine legend who once took down armed guerrillas
يقولون أنه أسطورة البحرية الذي قضى ذات مرة على رجال حرب العصابات المسلحين
with his bare hands and got a Hwarang Order of Military Merit for it.
بيديه العاريتين وحصل على وسام هوارانغ للاستحقاق العسكري لذلك.
And he's the kind of loose cannon who doesn't give a damn about higher-ups.
وهو من النوع الطليق الذي لا يبالي بالمسؤولين الأعلى منه.
So how do you plan on handling him, Mr. Baek?
إذًا كيف تخطط للتعامل معه يا سيد بايك؟
Don't worry, sir.
لا تقلق يا سيدي.
I'll take care of him myself.
سأعتني به بنفسي.
-[phone ringing] -[typewriters clacking]
-[رنين الهاتف] -[طقطقة الآلات الكاتبة]
[Kitae] Why don't you guys go out for a smoke?
[كيتاي] لماذا لا تخرجون للتدخين يا رفاق؟
-Sit. -[door closes]
-يجلس. -[يغلق الباب]
[groans]
[آهات]
-Everything good while I was away? -[agent] Yes, sir. All good.
-كل شيء جيد بينما كنت بعيدا؟ -[الوكيل] نعم يا سيدي. كل شيء جيد.
Listen, look into Prosecutor Jang Geonyoung
استمع، ابحث عن المدعي العام جانج جيون يونج
at the Busan District Prosecutors' Office.
في مكتب المدعي العام لمنطقة بوسان.
His background, family, relatives, friends, personality…
خلفيته، عائلته، أقاربه، أصدقائه، شخصيته...
Well, whatever it is, don't miss a single detail.
حسنًا، مهما كان الأمر، لا تفوت أي تفاصيل.
Dig up every last thing connected to him and bring it to me.
احفر كل شيء آخر مرتبط به وأحضره لي.
Yes, sir.
نعم يا سيدي.
[♪ tense music playing]
[♪ تشغيل موسيقى متوترة]
[John speaking in English] Ah. Nice to meet you. John Evans.
[يتحدث جون باللغة الإنجليزية] آه. سعيد بلقائك. جون إيفانز.
Just call me John.
فقط اتصل بي جون.
Okay, John.
حسنًا يا جون.
What are those bastards doing here?
ماذا يفعل هؤلاء الأوغاد هنا؟
Exercise. One hour per day.
يمارس. ساعة واحدة يوميا.
The murderers have rights too? Hmm?
القتلة لهم حقوق أيضاً؟ همم؟
Don't they in Korea?
أليس كذلك في كوريا؟
[Geonyoung scoffs]
[جونيونج يسخر]
[John] Let's get done with this quickly.
[جون] دعونا ننتهي من هذا بسرعة.
We've already provided enough information with the police regarding their cases.
لقد قدمنا ​​بالفعل معلومات كافية للشرطة فيما يتعلق بقضاياهم.
[in Korean] That's different, man.
[باللغة الكورية] هذا مختلف يا رجل.
[in English] Look.
[باللغة الإنجليزية] أنظر.
Hmm?
همم؟
In the corner. Here.
في الزاوية. هنا.
Something's written.
شيء مكتوب.
Remember the man you killed?
هل تتذكر الرجل الذي قتلته؟
He wrote it down when he was in the phone…
لقد كتب ذلك عندما كان في الهاتف ...
No. On the phone.
رقم على الهاتف.
Hmm?
همم؟
Any phone call when you were in the house?
هل هناك أي مكالمة هاتفية عندما كنت في المنزل؟
Uh… Mr. Kim picked up the phone and wrote something down on the paper.
اه... التقط السيد كيم الهاتف وكتب شيئًا ما على الورقة.
Okay.
تمام.
But…
لكن…
if you look at it,
إذا نظرت إليها،
there's no date.
ليس هناك تاريخ.
Only the time and place.
فقط الزمان والمكان.
It's a deal. A drug deal.
إنها صفقة. صفقة مخدرات.
Is there anything you heard about it?
هل هناك أي شيء سمعت عنه؟
These guys cannot understand Korean.
هؤلاء الرجال لا يستطيعون فهم اللغة الكورية.
Even if they heard something, they wouldn't know what it meant.
حتى لو سمعوا شيئًا، فلن يعرفوا ما يعنيه.
[in Korean] Yeah, I know. But I wanted to ask, just in case.
[باللغة الكورية] نعم، أعرف. ولكن أردت أن أسأل، فقط في حالة.
They should know a few words in Korean, now that they're in Korea.
يجب أن يعرفوا بضع كلمات باللغة الكورية، بعد أن أصبحوا في كوريا.
-So damn disrespectful. -[John speaking in English] What?
-لذلك عدم الاحترام لعنة. -[جون يتحدث باللغة الإنجليزية] ماذا؟
Okay.
تمام.
Now, you listen carefully. Hmm?
الآن، أنتم تستمعون بعناية. همم؟
To what I say.
على ما أقول.
"If you cooperate with me,
"إذا تعاونت معي،
I may be able to cut down your sentence.
قد أكون قادرا على خفض الجملة الخاصة بك.
Then you can be sent back to your country in a few years,
ومن ثم يمكن إعادتك إلى بلدك في غضون سنوات قليلة،
or I could even let you serve your sentence in the States."
أو يمكنني حتى أن أسمح لك بقضاء عقوبتك في الولايات المتحدة".
Understand?
يفهم؟
It's a deal!
إنها صفقة!
[soldier speaking in Korean] "See you tomorrow."
[جندي يتحدث باللغة الكورية] "أراك غدًا."
Mr. Kim said, "See you tomorrow."
قال السيد كيم: "أراك غدًا".
[in English] You speak Korean?
[باللغة الإنجليزية] هل تتحدث الكورية؟
[soldier] My girlfriend's Korean.
[جندي] صديقتي الكورية.
Tomorrow?
غداً؟
[in Korean] You sure?
[باللغة الكورية] أنت متأكد؟
-[in English] Tomorrow. -[in Korean] I'm sure.
-[باللغة الإنجليزية] غدا. -[باللغة الكورية] أنا متأكد.
[in English] Good job.
[باللغة الإنجليزية] عمل جيد.
[in Korean] Oh, right.
[باللغة الكورية] أوه، صحيح.
[In English] By the way…
[باللغة الإنجليزية] بالمناسبة...
The woman you killed, Lee Suni.
المرأة التي قتلتها، لي سوني.
She was pregnant.
كانت حاملا.
[♪ tense music playing]
[♪ تشغيل موسيقى متوترة]
[Geonyoung speaking in Korean] We've received intel
[جيونيونج يتحدث بالكورية] لقد تلقينا معلومات
that the meth dealers murdered last night,
أن تجار الميثامفيتامين قتلوا الليلة الماضية،
Kim Taeyeong and his wife, Lee Suni,
كيم تايونغ وزوجته لي سوني
had a deal lined up with their supplier today at 6:00 p.m.
كان لديهم صفقة مع مورديهم اليوم في الساعة 6:00 مساءً
at the Café C'est La Vie in Beomcheon-dong.
في مقهى C'est La Vie في Beomcheon-dong.
Assuming the supplier doesn't know they're dead yet, he's expected to show.
على افتراض أن المورد لا يعرف أنهم ماتوا بعد، فمن المتوقع أن يظهر ذلك.
Two of our investigators will pose as the couple on site
اثنان من محققينا سيتظاهرون بأنهما الزوجين في الموقع
and the moment he shows up, we move in for the arrest.
وفي اللحظة التي يظهر فيها، نتحرك للاعتقال.
[Yejin] Hello, I'm here.
[يجين] مرحبا، أنا هنا.
Ah, Ms. Oh!
آه، السيدة أوه!
Sir, this is Ms. Oh. She'll be playing the wife.
سيدي، هذه السيدة أوه. سوف تلعب دور الزوجة.
[Geonyoung grunts]
[همهمات جيونيونج]
Hello, sir.
أهلاً سيدي.
I'm Oh Yejin. I've just been assigned to the team.
أنا أوه يجين. لقد تم تعييني للتو في الفريق.
I'll be playing the wife, Lee Suni, in today's operation.
سألعب دور الزوجة، لي سوني، في عملية اليوم.
Right. Welcome aboard, Investigator Oh.
يمين. مرحبا بكم على متن الطائرة، المحقق أوه.
So… What about the husband?
إذن...ماذا عن الزوج؟
Right.
يمين.
That's me.
هذا أنا.
We'll need to find you a different husband.
سنحتاج إلى العثور على زوج مختلف لك.
I think that's a good idea, sir.
أعتقد أن هذه فكرة جيدة يا سيدي.
Wait, why? What's wrong?
انتظر، لماذا؟ ما هو الخطأ؟
[Geonyoung] Attention, everyone!
[جيونيونج] انتبهوا جميعًا!
All right,
حسنًا،
choose your husband from among them.
اختاري زوجك من بينهم.
[Investigator Kim] You think they're any better?
[المحقق كيم] هل تعتقد أنهم أفضل؟
[investigators clear throats]
[المحققون يطهرون الحلق]
What?
ماذا؟
[♪ mischievous music playing]
[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى المؤذية]
MUSIC CAFÉ C'EST LA VIE COFFEE & TEA
MUSIC CAFÉ C'EST LA VIE القهوة والشاي
[employee] Welcome.
[الموظف] مرحباً.
[Geonyoung, Yejin clear throats]
[جيونيونج، ييجين ينظفان الحلق]
[Geonyoung sighs]
[تنهد جيونيونج]
[phone ringing]
[رنين الهاتف]
C'est La Vie.
هذه هي الحياة.
Mr. Kim Taeyeong?
السيد كيم تايونغ؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
[man] Take Bus 57 and get off at Myeonhak-ri Station.
[رجل] استقل الحافلة رقم 57 وانزل في محطة ميونهاك-ري.
[Investigator Kim] Wait, too fast. Hey, slow down.
[المحقق كيم] انتظر بسرعة كبيرة. مهلا، أبطئ.
Slow down. Come on.
ابطئ. تعال.
[Yejin exhales sharply]
[يجين الزفير بحدة]
[Yejin] They're not going to lose us, right?
[يجين] لن يخسرونا، أليس كذلك؟
Just act natural.
فقط تصرف بشكل طبيعي.
Don't be so nervous.
لا تكن عصبيا جدا.
Right.
يمين.
Hmm.
همم.
Okay then.
حسنًا إذن.
Mind if I ask you something?
أتمانع إذا سألتك شيئاً؟
Sure, what is it?
بالتأكيد، ما هو؟
Well…
حسنًا…
Have you always been this good-looking, Mr. Jang?
هل كنت دائمًا بهذا المظهر الجميل يا سيد جانغ؟
Are you…
أنت…
hitting on me just to loosen up?
ضربني فقط للتخفيف؟
Come on, of course not.
هيا، بالطبع لا.
Someone like me hitting on you? No way.
شخص مثلي يهاجمك؟ مستحيل.
You think I'd make a fool of myself,
تظن أنني سأجعل من نفسي أحمقاً،
hitting on someone who's not interested? [chuckles]
ضرب شخص غير مهتم؟ [ضحكة مكتومة]
I must be losing my mind.
يجب أن أفقد عقلي.
My nerves have me speaking nonsense.
أعصابي تجعلني أتكلم هراء.
But I really did want to ask you that.
لكني أردت حقًا أن أسألك ذلك.
Just forget it. I'm sorry.
فقط ننسى ذلك. أنا آسف.
[chuckles]
[ضحكة مكتومة]
I hear you studied law at PNU and took the bar exam.
سمعت أنك درست القانون في جامعة الأميرة نورة وقدمت امتحان المحاماة.
Ah…
اه…
Yes, that's right.
نعم هذا صحيح.
[Geonyoung] Will you try again this year?
[Geonyoung] هل ستحاول مرة أخرى هذا العام؟
Well, that's…
حسنا، هذا...
Are you giving up?
هل تستسلم؟
Even if I pass, what's the point?
حتى لو نجحت، ما هي الفائدة؟
They'd never appoint a woman as a prosecutor.
لم يعينوا أبداً امرأة في منصب المدعي العام.
There isn't a single female prosecutor in this country yet.
لا يوجد مدعي عام واحد في هذا البلد حتى الآن.
Then why do you want to be one?
ثم لماذا تريد أن تكون واحدا؟
Mmm…
ط ط ...
What about you, Mr. Jang?
ماذا عنك يا سيد جانج؟
Why did you become a prosecutor?
لماذا أصبحت مدعيا عاما؟
[Geonyoung sighs]
[تنهد جيونيونج]
[♪ lively music playing]
[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى الحية]
MYEONHAK-RI
ميونهاك-ري
[Investigator Kim] Mr. Jang got off the bus.
[المحقق كيم] نزل السيد جانغ من الحافلة.
All right, just keep driving for now.
حسناً، فقط استمر بالقيادة الآن.
[investigator] Yes, sir.
[المحقق] نعم يا سيدي.
[Investigator Kim] Do they look like husband and wife?
[المحقق كيم] هل يبدوان مثل الزوج والزوجة؟
[investigator] Yeah, they look good together. Sure.
[المحقق] نعم، يبدوان جيدين معًا. بالتأكيد.
[Geonyoung sighs]
[تنهد جيونيونج]
[Geonyoung] Do you see anything?
[جيونيونج] هل ترى أي شيء؟
[Yejin] No, nothing. It's too dark.
[يجين] لا، لا شيء. انها مظلمة جدا.
Oh, right. You can't see a thing without your glasses, can you?
أوه، صحيح. لا يمكنك رؤية أي شيء بدون نظارتك، أليس كذلك؟
[Geonyoung] You are my eyes right now.
[Geonyoung] أنت عيني الآن.
-Look carefully. -[Yejin] Okay.
-انظر بعناية. -[يجين] حسنًا.
Look. That car! Here he comes!
ينظر. هذه السيارة! هنا يأتي!
Over there. That's him.
هناك. هذا هو.
[Yejin exhales sharply]
[يجين الزفير بحدة]
[Yejin sighs]
[تنهد يوجين]
[Geonyoung] Put your hands in your pockets and relax.
[Geonyoung] ضع يديك في جيوبك واسترخي.
-You're as stiff as a board. -[Yejin] Yes, sir.
-أنت قاسية مثل لوحة. -[يجين] نعم يا سيدي.
[Geonyoung] He looks familiar. Who is he?
[Geonyoung] يبدو مألوفا. من هو؟
[Yejin] Let's see the stuff first!
[يجين] دعونا نرى الأشياء أولا!
Let's see the cash first.
دعونا نرى النقدية أولا.
[clears throat]
[يمسح الحلق]
[Yejin] Well, this stuff is nice.
[يجين] حسنًا، هذه الأشياء لطيفة.
Yeah, good stuff.
نعم، أشياء جيدة.
[radio crackles while tuning]
[طقطقة الراديو أثناء الضبط]
[newscaster] Last night's brutal murder of a married couple in Haeundae
[مذيع إخباري] جريمة قتل وحشية ليلة أمس لزوجين في هايونداي
has been revealed to be the work of US soldiers
تم الكشف عن أنه من عمل الجنود الأمريكيين
who had been dealing meth with them.
الذي كان يتعامل معهم.
The victims, Kim and his wife, had a young daughter,
وكان لدى الضحايا، كيم وزوجته، ابنة صغيرة،
and it was discovered that she was present at the scene, adding to the shock.
واكتشف أنها كانت متواجدة في مكان الحادث، مما زاد من الصدمة.
The Busan Haeundae Police are focusing their investigation
وتركز شرطة بوسان هايونداي تحقيقاتها
on the possibility that the suspects committed the crime…
حول احتمالية أن يكون المشتبه فيهم قد ارتكبوا الجريمة..
[Daeil] Who the hell are you guys?
[دايل] من أنتم يا رفاق بحق الجحيم؟
[Geonyoung] This bastard.
[Geonyoung] هذا اللقيط.
I just remembered who he is.
لقد تذكرت للتو من هو.
[laughing]
[يضحك]
[both laughing]
[كلاهما يضحك]
[Yejin] Honey!
[يجين] العسل!
What the hell? Are you nuts? Who the hell are you?
بحق الجحيم؟ هل أنت مجنون؟ من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
[Yejin] He's asking who we are!
[يجين] إنه يسأل من نحن!
-You insane? -Can you believe this guy?
-أنت مجنون؟ -هل تصدق هذا الرجل؟
What the fuck?
ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
You're Kang Daeil, right?
أنت كانغ دايل، أليس كذلك؟
The Manjae Gang's underboss?
رئيس عصابة مانجاي؟
[scoffs]
[يسخر]
-[Daeil screaming] -[Yejin exclaims]
-[صراخ دايل] -[يهتف يجين]
-[struggling and brawling] -[metal grinding, tires screeching]
-[صراع وشجار] -[طحن المعادن، صرير الإطارات]
[Daeil] Hey!
[دايل] مهلا!
-[♪ thrilling music plays] -[Geonyoung and Yejin struggling]
-[♪ تشغيل موسيقى مثيرة] -[كفاح جيونيونج ويجين]
[Geonyoung] You son of a bitch! Hey!
[جيونيونج] أنت ابن العاهرة! يا!
[Yejin] Hey! Where do you think you're going?
[يجين] مهلا! إلى أين تعتقد أنك ذاهب؟
You bastard!
أيها الوغد!
[Geonyoung] Hey! You bastard!
[جيونيونج] مهلا! أيها الوغد!
-Hey! Stop, you bastard! -[Yejin] Stop right there!
-يا! توقف أيها الوغد! -[يجين] توقف هناك!
[Yejin yelps, groans]
[ييجي يصرخ، يتأوه]
Damn! That hurts.
اللعنة! هذا مؤلم.
Hey! Oh, stay right there!
يا! أوه، البقاء هناك!
Hey!
يا!
You're so dead!
أنت ميت جدا!
Get back here!
عد إلى هنا!
[Geonyoung] You son of a bitch!
[جيونيونج] أنت ابن العاهرة!
Hey!
يا!
Stop right there!
توقف هناك!
Where the hell do you think you're going?
أين بحق الجحيم تعتقد أنك ذاهب؟
Hey! You little shit!
يا! أنت القرف قليلا!
God, that son of a bitch. Fucking bastard.
الله ، هذا ابن العاهرة. لقيط سخيف.
Investigator Oh!
المحقق اه!
Investigator Oh! Stop right there!
المحقق اه! توقف هناك!
Shit, she's so damn fast. Fuck!
اللعنة، إنها سريعة جدًا. اللعنة!
For Christ's sake!
من أجل المسيح!
[Yejin] Where did he go?
[يجين] أين ذهب؟
Goddamn it!
اللعنة!
I'm going to kill that bastard!
انا ذاهب لقتل هذا اللقيط!
[Geonyoung] Investigator Oh!
[Geonyoung] المحقق أوه!
Investigator Oh!
المحقق اه!
-[shouts] -[exclaims]
-[يصرخ] -[يصرخ]
That girl's so damn relentless. Fucking hell.
تلك الفتاة لا هوادة فيها لعنة جدا. الجحيم اللعين.
[Geonyoung] Investigator Oh.
[Geonyoung] المحقق أوه.
Investigator Oh…
المحقق يا...
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Where the hell did he go?
أين ذهب بحق الجحيم؟
Damn, that bastard.
اللعنة، هذا اللقيط.
-[soft fart] -Huh?
-[ضرطة ناعمة] -هاه؟
[♪ stirring music plays]
[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى المثيرة]
Shit…
تبا…
Hey.
يا.
Paying respects to your ancestors?
هل تحترم أسلافك؟
What are you doing over there with your head on the ground?
ماذا تفعل هناك ورأسك على الأرض؟
[Daeil] For fuck's sake.
[دائيل] بحق اللعنة.
[Geonyoung] Hey, get out here. Come sit down.
[جيونيونج] مهلا، اخرج من هنا. تعال واجلس.
Fucking hell.
الجحيم اللعين.
Let's talk for a second, all right?
دعونا نتحدث لثانية، حسنا؟
Man, I'm fucking exhausted.
يا رجل، أنا سخيف استنفدت.
Goddamn it.
اللعنة.
You can run, huh?
يمكنك الركض، هاه؟
Where's Oh, my investigator?
أين يا محققي؟
[Daeil] Your investigator? How the fuck would I know!
[داعيل] محققك؟ كيف اللعنة سوف أعرف!
[Geonyoung] This asshole's got another knife. You little…
[Geonyoung] هذا الأحمق لديه سكين آخر. أنت قليلا…
[Geonyoung grunts]
[همهمات جيونيونج]
[Daeil] Wait! Hold up. Stop.
[دائيل] انتظر! أصمد. قف.
What?
ماذا؟
Shit.
القرف.
Come here! Get back here, you bastard!
تعال الى هنا! ارجع إلى هنا أيها الوغد!
Get back here! You little…
عد إلى هنا! أنت قليلا…
[Geonyoung shouts]
[يصرخ جيونيونج]
[Daeil groans]
[آهات دايل]
[Geonyoung] Give it a rest, jackass.
[Geonyoung] أعطها قسطا من الراحة، أيها الحمار.
How many damn knives do you have? Hey!
كم عدد السكاكين اللعينة لديك؟ يا!
Hey, you little… Son of a…
مهلا أيها الصغير...يا ابن...
You little shit.
أيها القرف الصغير.
-Get the hell off, asshole. -[Daeil shouts]
-اخرج من الجحيم أيها الأحمق. -[يصرخ دايل]
[Geonyoung] Damn it.
[جيونيونج] اللعنة.
[Geonyoung groans, grunts]
[آهات جيونيونج، همهمات]
You son of a bitch.
أنت ابن العاهرة.
[Yejin] Hey, you son of a bitch!
[يجين] مهلا، أنت ابن العاهرة!
You asshole!
أيها الأحمق!
Where do you think you're going?
إلى أين تعتقد أنك ذاهب؟
You bastard.
أيها الوغد.
-Huh? -[Daeil exclaims]
-هاه؟ -[يصيح دايل]
Investigator Oh.
المحقق اه.
-Did you use to work out? -My father's a tae kwon do master.
-هل كنت تستخدم للعمل بها؟ - والدي محترف في التايكوندو.
-Stay still, you asshole! -You're tough.
- ابقى ساكناً أيها الأحمق! -أنت صعبة.
[Yejin] I'll smash your face in.
[يجين] سأحطم وجهك.
Not at all. I'm soft as can be.
مُطْلَقاً. أنا ناعمة قدر الإمكان.
Don't ever do anything I didn't tell you to again.
لا تفعل أي شيء لم أخبرك به مرة أخرى.
Yes, sir. Understood.
نعم يا سيدي. مفهوم.
Get up.
استيقظ.
-I said, get up! -[groans]
-قلت اصعدي! -[آهات]
-[investigator 1] They're not up there. -[Investigator Kim] No? Not there either?
-[المحقق 1] إنهم ليسوا هناك. -[المحقق كيم] لا؟ ليس هناك أيضا؟
[investigator 2] I don't think they're here.
[المحقق 2] لا أعتقد أنهم هنا.
[Investigator Kim] Go check up there. This way.
[المحقق كيم] اذهب لتفقد هناك. من هنا.
-[investigator 2] Up there? -Yeah, go take a look.
-[المحقق 2] هناك؟ -نعم، اذهب وألقي نظرة.
-[investigators] Mr. Jang! Mr. Jang! -Damn.
-[المحققون] السيد جانغ! السيد جانج! -اللعنة.
Mr. Jang!
السيد جانج!
You know,
أنت تعرف،
if you get locked up this time,
إذا تم حبسك هذه المرة،
it's 10 years minimum.
إنه 10 سنوات كحد أدنى.
Fuck.
اللعنة.
Ten years just for pushing some meth? I don't think so.
عشر سنوات فقط لترويج بعض الميثامفيتامين؟ أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
It's not like I killed anyone.
ليس الأمر وكأنني قتلت أحداً.
I'll probably be out in a couple.
ربما سأكون بالخارج في غضون بضعة.
Bullshit.
هراء.
The Manjae Gang's number two, out selling drugs himself?
الرجل الثاني في عصابة مانجاي، الذي يبيع المخدرات بنفسه؟
Why would you do that, huh?
لماذا تفعل ذلك، هاه؟
What are they saying?
ماذا يقولون؟
Hey.
يا.
You've been sneaking out drugs behind Jo Manjae's back, haven't you?
لقد كنت تتسلل المخدرات خلف ظهر جو مانجاي، أليس كذلك؟
If he finds out…
إذا اكتشف…
you think he'll let you get away with it?
هل تعتقد أنه سيتركك تفلت من العقاب؟
His number two stealing his stash?
الرجل الثاني الذي يسرق مخبأه؟
Fucking hell.
الجحيم اللعين.
So what do you want?
إذن ماذا تريد؟
[Geonyoung] Listen carefully.
[Geonyoung] استمع بعناية.
The thing is,
الأمر هو،
it's Jo Manjae that I really want.
إنه جو مانجاي الذي أريده حقًا.
Which means you can save yourself
مما يعني أنه يمكنك إنقاذ نفسك
if you just do what I say.
إذا كنت فقط تفعل ما أقول.
You want me to be a goddamn rat?
هل تريد مني أن أكون فأراً لعيناً؟
If I get caught, I'm the only one fucked.
إذا تم القبض علي، فأنا الوحيد الذي مارس الجنس.
So why should I?
فلماذا ينبغي لي؟
Damn it, you thick-headed idiot.
اللعنة عليك، أيها الأحمق ذو الرأس السميك.
Hey.
يا.
You dumbass. Does your brain even work? Hmm?
أنت غبي. هل يعمل دماغك حتى؟ همم؟
Do you not get who's holding your leash right now?
ألا تفهم من يمسك مقودك الآن؟
I don't want the small fry with a kilo or two.
لا أريد الزريعة الصغيرة التي تحتوي على كيلو أو اثنين.
I want 10 kilos or more, the kind of deal Manjae handles himself.
أريد 10 كيلوغرامات أو أكثر، هذا النوع من الصفقات الذي يتعامل معه مانجاي بنفسه.
The choice is yours.
الخيار لك.
Be a goddamn rat,
كن فأرًا لعينًا،
or die at Jo Manjae's hands.
أو تموت على يدي جو مانجاي.
Investigator Oh.
المحقق اه.
The key.
المفتاح.
-[Yejin] What key? -[Geonyoung] To the handcuffs.
-[يجين] أي مفتاح؟ -[Geonyoung] إلى الأصفاد.
[Yejin] Why?
[يجين] لماذا؟
Huh? Huh?
هاه؟ هاه؟
Huh?
هاه؟
What…
ماذا…
Get out of here. Go.
اخرج من هنا. يذهب.
[Yejin] What? Oh!
[يجين] ماذا؟ أوه!
Mr. Jang! What the hell are you doing?
السيد جانج! ماذا تفعل بحق الجحيم؟
-I let him go. -Why?
-لقد تركته يذهب. -لماذا؟
[Geonyoung] This stays between you and me.
[Geonyoung] هذا يبقى بيني وبينك.
It's our little secret.
إنه سرنا الصغير.
[Kitae] His mother is dead.
[كيتاي] والدته ماتت.
He's got a father and a younger sister.
لديه أب وأخت أصغر منه.
[agent] Yes, the father's name is Jang Myeongho.
[الوكيل] نعم، اسم الأب هو جانغ ميونغهو.
He's in a psychiatric hospital.
إنه في مستشفى للأمراض النفسية.
[Kitae] Psychiatric hospital?
[كيتاي] مستشفى للأمراض النفسية؟
[agent] He's been there a long time, about 20 years.
[الوكيل] لقد كان هناك لفترة طويلة، حوالي 20 عامًا.
[Kitae] What for?
[كيتاي] لماذا؟
[agent] I'm looking into it.
[وكيل] أنا أبحث في الأمر.
[Kitae] What about his sister?
[كيتاي] ماذا عن أخته؟
[agent] Jang Hyeeun, 25 years old.
[الوكيل] جانغ هيون، 25 عامًا.
She works at a dye factory in Gyeonggi-do. There's nothing unusual about her.
تعمل في مصنع صبغ في جيونجي دو. لا يوجد شيء غير عادي عنها.
Check the people around him too.
تحقق من الأشخاص من حوله أيضًا.
Report back if you find anything useful.
قم بالإبلاغ إذا وجدت أي شيء مفيد.
[agent] Yes, sir.
[الوكيل] نعم يا سيدي.
And about Ikeda Yuji, the one you mentioned last time.
وعن إيكيدا يوجي، الذي ذكرته في المرة السابقة.
Did you look into her?
هل نظرت إليها؟
[agent] Her real name is Choi Yuji.
[الوكيل] اسمها الحقيقي هو تشوي يوجي.
She's a Zainichi.
إنها زينيتشي.
A Zainichi?
زينيتشي ؟
[agent] Yes, she lost both her parents when she was 13.
[وكيل] نعم، لقد فقدت والديها عندما كان عمرها 13 عامًا.
Then Chairman Ikeda adopted her.
ثم تبناها الرئيس إيكيدا.
He seems to put a lot of trust in her.
يبدو أنه يثق بها كثيرًا.
She's got real pull in the organization,
لديها تأثير حقيقي في المنظمة،
with plenty of people gunning for her.
مع الكثير من الناس يطلقون النار عليها.
Choi Yuji.
تشوي يوجي.
[in Japanese] I'll see you again.
[باللغة اليابانية] سوف أراك مرة أخرى.
[engine turns over]
[ينقلب المحرك]
[in Korean] Look at that idiot.
[باللغة الكورية] انظر إلى هذا الأحمق.
[agent] But why are you looking into Choi Yuji?
[الوكيل] ولكن لماذا تبحث عن تشوي يوجي؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Choi Yuji…
تشوي يوجي…
[agent] While you were out earlier, Mr. Baek Kihyun called.
[العميل] بينما كنت بالخارج سابقًا، اتصل بك السيد بايك كيهيون.
[Kitae] What did he say?
[كيتاي] ماذا قال؟
[agent] He's coming today for your mother's memorial.
[العميل] سيأتي اليوم لحضور حفل تأبين والدتك.
He said he couldn't make it.
قال إنه لا يستطيع فعل ذلك.
He's in the army, right?
إنه في الجيش، أليس كذلك؟
Top of his class at the Military Academy.
الأول على دفعته في الكلية الحربية.
[agent] Top of his class…
[الوكيل] الأفضل في فئته...
It's just a matter of time before he pins on a star, right?
إنها مجرد مسألة وقت قبل أن يعلق على نجمة، أليس كذلك؟
A star? Sure, he'll get one.
نجم؟ بالتأكيد، سوف يحصل على واحدة.
The question is, how many.
السؤال هو كم عددهم؟
[Kitae] Hey, Baek Kihyun.
[كيتاي] مرحبًا، بيك كيهيون.
[cup thuds softly]
[يضرب الكأس بهدوء]
[Kitae] Let's eat.
[كيتاي] دعونا نأكل.
[Kihyun] Thank you for the meal.
[كيهيون] شكرا لك على الوجبة.
Kihyun was only in first or second grade when Mom passed.
كان كيهيون في الصف الأول أو الثاني فقط عندما توفيت أمي.
Time really flies. Doesn't it, Kitae?
الوقت يطير حقا. أليس كذلك، كيتاي؟
[Kitae] How's life in the army? Doing all right?
[كيتاي] كيف هي الحياة في الجيش؟ هل كل شيء على ما يرام؟
[Kihyun] I'm doing fine.
[كيهيون] أنا بخير.
[Kitae] Is something up?
[كيتاي] هل هناك شيء ما؟
I wish it were.
أتمنى لو كان.
[Kitae] Staring at barbed wire on the front line is boring, no?
[كيتاي] التحديق في الأسلاك الشائكة على الخط الأمامي أمر ممل، أليس كذلك؟
SECURITY COMMAND AHN SEUNGHYEOK
القيادة الأمنية آهن سيونغهيوك
He'll let you know once a spot opens up at Security Command.
سيخبرك بمجرد فتح مكان في قيادة الأمن.
You always wanted to go there after graduating the academy.
كنت دائما تريد الذهاب إلى هناك بعد التخرج من الأكاديمية.
I can take care of myself.
أستطيع الاعتناء بنفسي.
Just let me help you. What are big brothers for?
فقط دعني أساعدك. لماذا الاخوة الكبار؟
Right, Soyeong?
صحيح، سويونغ؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
But you know, Kihyun's all grown up now.
لكن كما تعلمون، كيهيون كبر الآن.
His opinion matters too.
رأيه يهم أيضا.
[Kitae] Just take it.
[كيتاي] فقط خذها.
I'm sure plenty of others got his card.
أنا متأكد من أن الكثير من الآخرين حصلوا على بطاقته.
I told you.
أخبرتك.
In the end, guys with money and connections run the world.
في النهاية، الرجال الذين يملكون المال والعلاقات هم من يديرون العالم.
[Soyeong] That's true. Life is brutal without parents or connections.
[سويونغ] هذا صحيح. الحياة وحشية بدون الوالدين أو العلاقات.
But things get easier if you have money and power.
لكن الأمور تصبح أسهل إذا كان لديك المال والسلطة.
Funny how that works.
مضحك كيف يعمل ذلك.
Kitae.
كيتاي.
I can take care of myself.
أستطيع الاعتناء بنفسي.
Fine.
بخير.
Let me know if you change your mind.
اسمحوا لي أن أعرف إذا غيرت رأيك.
[Yejin sighs]
[تنهد يوجين]
So, your plan is to use Kang Daeil as a mole to get Jo Manjae?
إذًا، خطتك هي استخدام كانغ دايل كجاسوس للحصول على جو مانجاي؟
[Geonyoung] Yes.
[جيونيونج] نعم.
[Yejin] But what if Kang Daeil doesn't play along and just disappears on you?
[يجين] لكن ماذا لو لم ينسجم كانغ دايل معك واختفى أمامك؟
-What are you going to do then? -[chuckles]
-ماذا ستفعل بعد ذلك؟ -[ضحكة مكتومة]
He'll have no choice but to do as I say if he wants to stay alive.
لن يكون أمامه خيار سوى أن يفعل ما أقوله إذا كان يريد البقاء على قيد الحياة.
How can you be so sure?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون متأكدا جدا؟
Because Kang Daeil, that punk,
لأن كانغ دايل، ذلك الشرير،
has been skimming drugs behind his boss's back.
كان يقشط المخدرات خلف ظهر رئيسه.
It means being a number two isn't enough for him.
وهذا يعني أن كونه رقم اثنين لا يكفي بالنسبة له.
What are you…
ماذا أنت…
I promised him
لقد وعدته
I'd make him number one in the gang.
سأجعله رقم واحد في العصابة
Once I take down Jo Manjae,
بمجرد أن أسقط جو مانجاي،
Kang Daeil becomes the boss of the gang.
كانغ دايل يصبح رئيس العصابة.
[Yejin] So then,
[يجين] إذًا،
you're going to take down Jo Manjae, but really just let Kang Daeil walk free?
هل ستقوم بالقضاء على جو مانجاي، ولكن في الحقيقة ستترك كانغ دايل يمشي حرًا؟
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى الغامضة]
First, I take down Jo Manjae.
أولاً، أسقط جو مانجاي.
Then, I'll put Kang Daeil behind bars too.
إذن، سأضع كانغ دايل خلف القضبان أيضًا.
[Yejin] Mr. Jang.
[يجين] السيد جانغ.
Yeah.
نعم.
You know Alain Delon, right?
أنت تعرف آلان ديلون، أليس كذلك؟
Alain Delon? What about him?
آلان ديلون؟ ماذا عنه؟
You know, in those movies,
كما تعلمون، في تلك الأفلام،
he goes around killing people brutally with that handsome face.
يتجول ويقتل الناس بوحشية بهذا الوجه الوسيم.
And then he smokes, just like you are right now.
ومن ثم يدخن، كما تفعل أنت الآن.
Yeah. That's it.
نعم. هذا كل شيء.
Every time I watch him, I get butterflies for some reason.
في كل مرة أشاهده، أشعر بالفراشات لسبب ما.
People must tell you all the time you look like him, right?
يجب أن يخبرك الناس طوال الوقت أنك تشبهه، أليس كذلك؟
[Geonyoung] Enough with the nonsense.
[جيونيونج] كفى هراء.
Take a look at this photo.
نلقي نظرة على هذه الصورة.
[Geonyoung sighs]
[تنهد جيونيونج]
That guy next to Jo Manjae.
ذلك الرجل بجانب جو مانجاي.
[Yejin] Looks like Jo Manjae's bowing and scraping to him.
[Yejin] يبدو أن جو مانجاي ينحني ويخدش له.
Who's the guy, his backer?
من هو الرجل، مؤيده؟
[Geonyoung] We'll know who he is once we've got Jo Manjae.
[Geonyoung] سنعرف من هو بمجرد أن نحصل على جو مانجاي.
[Yejin sighs]
[تنهد يوجين]
Wow, there's another Alain Delon here.
واو، هناك آلان ديلون آخر هنا.
[Geonyoung] Just how many Alain Delons do you see exactly?
[Geonyoung] كم عدد آلان ديلون الذي تراه بالضبط؟
Me? Only one, of course.
أنا؟ واحد فقط بالطبع.
Cheers.
هتافات.
[exhales sharply]
[الزفير بحدة]
[clears throat]
[يمسح الحلق]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى المشؤومة]
9TH, 8 P.M. ROOM 611, BUSAN HOTEL
التاسع، الثامنة مساءً، الغرفة رقم 611، فندق بوسان
[lighter clicks open]
[فتح النقرات الخفيفة]
[phone ringing]
[رنين الهاتف]
Ms. Oh, the phone.
السيدة أوه، الهاتف.
-Hello? -[man] Is this the Chinese restaurant?
-مرحبًا؟ -[رجل] هل هذا هو المطعم الصيني؟
No, it's not.
لا، ليس كذلك.
-[voice] Sorry about that. -[line disconnects]
-[صوت] آسف لذلك. -[انقطع الخط]
What the hell?
بحق الجحيم؟
Is there something wrong with our number?
هل هناك خطأ ما في رقمنا؟
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
[Yejin] Well, we keep getting wrong numbers.
[يجين] حسنًا، نحن نستمر في الحصول على أرقام خاطئة.
Someone else called earlier asking if this was a bathhouse.
اتصل شخص آخر في وقت سابق وسأل عما إذا كان هذا حمامًا.
It's so weird.
انه غريب جدا.
[Investigator Kim] Let's go eat.
[المحقق كيم] دعنا نذهب لتناول الطعام.
[investigators] Yes, sir.
[المحققون] نعم يا سيدي.
[Investigator Kim groaning]
[المحقق كيم يئن]
What should we have today?
ماذا يجب أن يكون لدينا اليوم؟
[investigator 1] Man, I'm starving.
[المحقق 1] يا رجل، أنا أتضور جوعا.
[investigator 2] Pork and rice soup? What do you think?
[المحقق 2] حساء لحم الخنزير والأرز؟ ماذا تعتقد؟
[investigator 1] But we had it yesterday.
[المحقق 1] لكن حصلنا عليه بالأمس.
-[investigator 2] You're right. -[investigator 1] How about a set meal?
-[المحقق 2] أنت على حق. -[المحقق 1] ماذا عن الوجبة المحددة؟
[Investigator Kim] Sounds good to me.
[المحقق كيم] يبدو جيدًا بالنسبة لي.
[Yejin] Wait for me!
[يجين] انتظرني!
How about jjajangmyeon?
ماذا عن جاجانغميون؟
[phone ringing]
[رنين الهاتف]
[ringing tone]
[نغمة الرنين]
[agent] No answer.
[الوكيل] لا جواب.
[♪ tense, menacing music plays]
[♪ تشغيل موسيقى متوترة وخطيرة]
PROSECUTION SERVICE
خدمة النيابة العامة
BUSAN DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
مكتب المدعي العام في منطقة بوسان
[door swings open]
[يتأرجح الباب مفتوحا]
PERSONAL RECORD NAME: KANG DAEIL
اسم السجل الشخصي: كانغ دايل
NAME: JO MANJAE
اسم السجل الشخصي: جو مانجاي
[Kitae scoffs] Look at all this crap.
[كيتاي يسخر] انظر إلى كل هذا الهراء.
CASE FILE: PORT OF BUSAN METH SMUGGLING
ملف القضية: تهريب مخدرات في ميناء بوسان
CASE FILE: THE MANJAE GANG
ملف القضية: عصابة مانجاي
[chief prosecutor] Hey, Jang.
[رئيس النيابة] مرحبًا، جانج.
Join me for lunch.
انضم إلي لتناول طعام الغداء.
I'm meeting with the chief editor of Joguk Ilbo.
سأقابل رئيس تحرير جوجوك إلبو.
-You haven't eaten yet, have you? -Oh, dear. I just ate, actually.
-أنت لم تأكل بعد، أليس كذلك؟ -يا عزيزي. لقد أكلت للتو، في الواقع.
Yeah? Then drop by my office later.
نعم؟ ثم قم بزيارة مكتبي لاحقًا.
-I've got something to tell you. -[Geonyoung] Yes, sir.
-لدي شيء لأخبرك به. -[جيونيونج] نعم يا سيدي.
Right. I'll be tied up questioning suspects this afternoon.
يمين. سأكون مقيدًا في استجواب المشتبه بهم بعد ظهر هذا اليوم.
I'll come by tomorrow morning.
سآتي صباح الغد.
-[chief prosecutor] All right. -[Geonyoung] Yeah.
- [رئيس النيابة] حسنًا. -[جيونيونج] نعم.
Hey, Jang! You'd better show up!
مهلا، جانج! من الأفضل أن تظهر!
[Kitae] Let's clear out.
[كيتاي] دعونا نخرج.
[door swings open]
[يتأرجح الباب مفتوحا]
[Geonyoung humming]
[همهمة جيونيونج]
[vocalizes]
[ينطق]
[Kitae sighs]
[تنهد كيتاي]
[Geonyoung humming, vocalizing]
[همهمة جيونيونغ، غناء]
[Geonyoung vocalizing]
[غناء جيونيونج]
Looks like everyone thoughtlessly ran off to lunch once again,
يبدو أن الجميع هربوا بلا تفكير لتناول الغداء مرة أخرى،
with papers lying around and the door unlocked.
مع الأوراق متناثرة والباب مفتوح.
And you are?
وأنت؟
[Kitae] I'm Baek Kitae, KCIA Busan branch.
[كاتي] أنا أستمتع كيت، كي سي آي بوسن.
-[♪ ominous music playing] -[Geonyoung] This guy's name
-[♪ تشغيل موسيقى مشؤومة] -[Geonyoung] اسم هذا الرجل
is Baek Kitae.
هو بايك كيتاي.
That guy next to Jo Manjae.
ذلك الرجل بجانب جو مانجاي.
[Geonyoung] He's with the KCIA?
[Geonyoung] هل هو مع KCIA؟
Jang Geonyoung, Busan District Prosecutors' Office.
جانغ جيونيونج، مكتب المدعي العام لمنطقة بوسان.
So, what brings the KCIA all the way here?
إذًا، ما الذي جلب وكالة KCIA إلى هنا؟
There must be a reason
يجب أن يكون هناك سبب
you're standing in the middle of someone else's office while they're out.
أنت تقف في منتصف مكتب شخص آخر أثناء تواجده بالخارج.
You know Jo Manjae, right?
أنت تعرف جو مانجاي، أليس كذلك؟
The Manjae Gang's number one.
رقم واحد في عصابة مانجاي.
Right, the Manjae Gang.
صحيح، عصابة مانجاي.
I came here
جئت إلى هنا
to ask you to drop Jo Manjae. Lay off him.
لأطلب منك إسقاط جو مانجاي. الاستغناء عنه.
You're telling me to shut down my investigation?
هل تطلب مني إيقاف تحقيقاتي؟
The KCIA
KCIA
giving orders to a prosecutor?
إعطاء الأوامر للنيابة؟
I didn't mean it like that.
لم أقصد ذلك من هذا القبيل.
[Geonyoung] Then what?
[جيونيونج] ثم ماذا؟
At least give me a proper explanation.
على الأقل أعطني تفسيرا مناسبا.
[Kitae] Did you know Jo Manjae's married to a Zainichi?
[كيتاي] هل تعلم أن جو مانجاي متزوج من زينيتشي؟
Yes.
نعم.
According to our recent intel,
وفقا لمعلوماتنا الأخيرة،
his wife has been deeply involved with North Korea.
كانت زوجته متورطة بعمق في كوريا الشمالية.
[Geonyoung] Ah.
[جيونيونج] آه.
So Jo Manjae is tangled up with commies now, huh?
إذن جو مانجاي متشابك مع الشيوعيين الآن، أليس كذلك؟
[Kitae] We got word that his gang's been pushing meth up North through Japan.
[كيتاي] لقد حصلنا على معلومات تفيد بأن عصابته تقوم بترويج الميثامفيتامين في الشمال عبر اليابان.
We've been running an operation on this for over a year now.
لقد قمنا بإجراء عملية على هذا منذ أكثر من عام الآن.
I went undercover to make contact with Jo Manjae myself.
لقد ذهبت متخفيًا للتواصل مع جو مانجاي بنفسي.
[Geonyoung] So you're saying, the KCIA's already working him,
[Geonyoung] إذًا أنت تقول، وكالة المخابرات المركزية KCIA تعمل معه بالفعل،
and I'm supposed to back off?
ومن المفترض أن أتراجع؟
We're all civil servants here.
نحن جميعا موظفون حكوميون هنا.
We should help one another, shouldn't we?
يجب علينا أن نساعد بعضنا البعض، أليس كذلك؟
It's all for the country after all.
كل شيء من أجل البلاد بعد كل شيء.
[Geonyoung sighs]
[تنهد جيونيونج]
Okay!
تمام!
Got it.
فهمتها.
I'll leave Jo Manjae to you then.
سأترك جو مانجاي لك إذن.
That goddamn commie.
ذلك الشيوعي اللعين.
[Kitae] Thank you for understanding.
[كيتاي] شكرا لتفهمك.
Gosh, don't mention it.
يا إلهي، لا تذكر ذلك.
[Kitae] You moved to Busan about two months ago, right?
[كيتاي] انتقلت إلى بوسان منذ حوالي شهرين، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah, that's right.
نعم هذا صحيح.
You're from Seoul, so I bet it hasn't been easy settling in here.
أنت من سيول، لذا أراهن أنه لم يكن من السهل الاستقرار هنا.
We should grab some raw fish sometime.
يجب أن نلتقط بعض الأسماك النيئة في وقت ما.
I'll take you someplace nice.
سآخذك إلى مكان لطيف.
[Geonyoung] Ah, actually…
[جيونيونج] اه، في الواقع...
I'm not really into raw fish.
أنا لست حقا في الأسماك النيئة.
When we get the chance,
وعندما تتاح لنا الفرصة،
let's have some soju instead, with pork and rice soup.
دعنا نتناول بعض السوجو بدلاً من ذلك، مع حساء لحم الخنزير والأرز.
That sounds good too.
هذا يبدو جيدًا أيضًا.
All right, then. I'll give you a call.
حسنًا إذن. سأعطيك مكالمة.
Jo Manjae is…
جو مانجاي ...
tied up with commies, huh?
مرتبطة مع الشيوعيين، هاه؟
[laughing]
[يضحك]
Yeah, right.
نعم صحيح.
Who the hell does he think he's fooling?
من بحق الجحيم يعتقد أنه يخدع؟
[vocalizing]
[غناء]
[whistling]
[صفير]
-Let's go eat. -[agent] Yes, sir.
-دعونا نذهب لتناول الطعام. -[الوكيل] نعم يا سيدي.
[sighs] Mr. Jang isn't here yet.
[تنهدات] السيد جانغ ليس هنا بعد.
-[Geonyoung] Turn the lights off. -Damn, you scared me.
-[Geonyoung] أطفئ الأضواء. -اللعنة، لقد أخافتني.
[Geonyoung] It's broad daylight.
[Geonyoung] إنه وضح النهار.
[Yejin] I didn't see you there.
[يجين] لم أراك هناك.
Save if you want a better life.
احفظ إذا كنت تريد حياة أفضل.
[Yejin] Well, I picked up some lunch for you.
[يجين] حسنًا، لقد أحضرت لك بعض الغداء.
Have you eaten yet?
هل أكلت بعد؟
[Geonyoung] No.
[جيونيونج] لا.
Where's Mr. Kim and…
أين السيد كيم و...
Where is everyone?
أين الجميع؟
[Yejin] He said he was going to court.
[يجين] قال إنه سيذهب إلى المحكمة.
The other investigators are out at the scene.
المحققون الآخرون في مكان الحادث.
[Yejin sighs]
[تنهد يوجين]
[Geonyoung chewing]
[مضغ جيونيونج]
[Yejin] Were you hungry? [chuckles]
[يجين] هل كنت جائعا؟ [ضحكة مكتومة]
Slow down, or you'll get indigestion.
تمهل وإلا ستصاب بعسر الهضم.
-[Geonyoung] Here. Take a look. -[paper rustling]
-[جيونيونج] هنا. ألق نظرة. -[ حفيف الورق ]
What's this?
ما هذا؟
[cup thuds]
[قرع الكأس]
9TH, 8 P.M. ROOM 611, BUSAN HOTEL
التاسع، الثامنة مساءً، الغرفة رقم 611، فندق بوسان
He says the Yakuza's coming to Busan.
يقول أن الياكوزا قادمون إلى بوسان.
[Yejin] The Yakuza?
[يجين] ياكوزا؟
Yes.
نعم.
[Geonyoung] He's meeting Jo Manjae at Busan Hotel.
[Geonyoung] سيلتقي بجو مانجاي في فندق بوسان.
[Yejin] Uh… It's about the meth, right?
[يجين] اه... الأمر يتعلق بالميثامفيتامين، أليس كذلك؟
That's what it looks like.
هذا ما يبدو عليه الأمر.
[Yejin] Damn.
[يجين] اللعنة.
This time…
هذه المرة…
we have to get Jo Manjae.
علينا أن نحصل على جو مانجاي.
[Yejin] Hang on.
[يجين] انتظر.
The 9th?
التاسع؟
That's the day after tomorrow, isn't it?
هذا هو بعد غد، أليس كذلك؟
[Geonyoung] That's right. The day after tomorrow.
[جيونيونج] هذا صحيح. بعد غد.
Oh, right. The KCIA was here earlier.
أوه، صحيح. كانت KCIA هنا في وقت سابق.
-[Yejin] The KCIA? W-Why? -Yeah.
-[يجين] وكالة المخابرات المركزية؟ ث-لماذا؟ -نعم.
What business…
ما الأعمال…
could they possibly have
هل يمكن أن يكون لديهم
here at the Busan District Prosecutors' Office?
هنا في مكتب المدعي العام لمنطقة بوسان؟
[Yejin] What could've brought the KCIA here?
[يجين] ما الذي جلب وكالة المخابرات المركزية الكورية إلى هنا؟
[Geonyoung] Exactly. What could've brought them here?
[جيونيونج] بالضبط. ما الذي قد أتى بهم إلى هنا؟
Look at this guy.
انظر إلى هذا الرجل.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى المنذرة]
[siren wailing in distance]
[صافرة الإنذار تبكي من مسافة]
[Investigator Kim breathing heavily]
[المحقق كيم يتنفس بشدة]
[Daeil] Boss, he's here.
[دائيل] أيها الزعيم، إنه هنا.
[Manjae] Yeah? All right.
[مانجاي] نعم؟ حسنًا.
Pleasure to meet you. I'm Jo Manjae.
يسعدني مقابلتك. أنا جو مانجاي.
[Daeil translates into Japanese]
[دايل يترجم إلى اليابانية]
[Investigator Kim coughs]
[المحقق كيم يسعل]
[Yakuza speaking in Japanese]
[ياكوزا يتحدث باللغة اليابانية]
[Daeil] He says hello.
[دائيل] يقول مرحبا.
-[Manjae] Have a seat. -[Daeil translates into Japanese]
-[مانجاي] تفضل بالجلوس. - [ترجمة الدايل إلى اليابانية]
[Yakuza speaking in Japanese]
[ياكوزا يتحدث باللغة اليابانية]
[Yakuza sighs]
[تنهد ياكوزا]
So, is this your first time in Busan?
هل هذه هي المرة الأولى لك في بوسان؟
[translates into Japanese]
[مترجم إلى اليابانية]
[speaks in Japanese]
[يتحدث باليابانية]
[Daeil] He used to live here as a kid.
[دائيل] كان يعيش هنا عندما كان طفلاً.
-[Manjae] So he's a Zainichi? -[Daeil translates into Japanese]
-[مانجاي] إذن هو زينيتشي؟ - [ترجمة الدايل إلى اليابانية]
[Yakuza speaking in Japanese]
[ياكوزا يتحدث باللغة اليابانية]
-[♪ tense music playing] -[Yakuza speaking in Japanese]
-[♪ تشغيل موسيقى متوترة] -[ياكوزا يتحدث باللغة اليابانية]
He's Japanese, and he was here in 1944.
إنه ياباني، وكان هنا في عام 1944.
That's before liberation.
وذلك قبل التحرير.
My grandfather was killed by a Jap bullet at the Battle of Cheongsan-ri, you know.
لقد قُتل جدي برصاصة يابانية في معركة تشيونغسان ري، كما تعلم.
[Daeil] Uh…
[دايل] اه...
[in Japanese] Well…
[باللغة اليابانية] حسنًا...
[sneezes]
[العطس]
[in Korean] Well, never mind.
[باللغة الكورية] حسنًا، لا يهم.
History's history, and business is business, eh?
التاريخ تاريخ، والعمل هو العمل، أليس كذلك؟
Go get the stuff.
اذهب للحصول على الاشياء.
[Daeil speaking in Japanese] Uh… We'll bring it to you now.
[دايل يتحدث باليابانية] اه... سنحضره لك الآن.
Looks good.
تبدو جيدة.
But…
لكن…
you think you can move 10 kilos every month?
هل تعتقد أنه يمكنك نقل 10 كيلوغرامات كل شهر؟
[in Korean] He's asking if we can do 10 kilos every month.
[باللغة الكورية] إنه يسأل إذا كان بإمكاننا خسارة 10 كيلوغرامات كل شهر.
[Manjae] Let's see the cash first.
[مانجاي] دعونا نرى النقود أولاً.
[Daeil translates into Japanese]
[دايل يترجم إلى اليابانية]
[Yakuza] Hey.
[ياكوزا] مهلا.
[clattering]
[قعقعة]
[Manjae] Tell him we can do 20 kilos.
[مانجاي] أخبره أنه يمكننا أن نزيد 20 كيلو.
[Daeil translates into Japanese]
[دايل يترجم إلى اليابانية]
[Yakuza speaking in Japanese] That's impressive.
[ياكوزا يتحدث باليابانية] هذا مثير للإعجاب.
[Manjae] "Sugoi"?
[مانجاي] "سوغوي"؟
[Daeil speaking in Korean] "Sugoi" means "impressive."
[دايل يتحدث بالكورية] "سوغوي" تعني "مثير للإعجاب".
[Manjae speaking in Japanese] Cheers.
[مانجاي يتحدث باليابانية] تحياتي.
[Geonyoung scoffs]
[جونيونج يسخر]
[Geonyoung speaking in Korean] Sounds like they're hitting it off, huh?
[جيونيونج يتحدث بالكورية] يبدو أنهم ينجحون في ذلك، هاه؟
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى المشوقة]
All right.
حسنًا.
I'd say we're good to go.
أود أن أقول أننا على ما يرام.
We got it on tape, right?
لقد سجلناها على الشريط، أليس كذلك؟
All right.
حسنًا.
Everyone, grab your gear. Let's go.
الجميع، الاستيلاء على المعدات الخاصة بك. دعنا نذهب.
Move in.
انتقل للعيش.
[investigators exclaiming, murmuring]
[المحققون يصرخون، يتذمرون]
[investigator] Turn the light on. The light.
[المحقق] أشعل الضوء. ضوء.
[Yejin] I think it's a blackout. What do we do?
[Yejin] أعتقد أنه انقطاع التيار الكهربائي. ماذا نفعل؟
[investigators exclaiming]
[صرخة المحققين]
-[Daeil] Hey, go see what's going on. -[gang member] Yes, sir.
-[دائيل] مهلا، اذهب لترى ما الذي يحدث. -[عضو العصابة] نعم يا سيدي.
-[agent grunts] -[gang member groans]
-[همهمات العميل] -[آهات أعضاء العصابة]
[clamoring]
[الصراخ]
What the hell?
بحق الجحيم؟
[agent 1] Stop resisting, you bastards!
[العميل 1] توقفوا عن المقاومة أيها الأوغاد!
-[agent 2] On your knees, punk! -[agent 3] On your knees!
-[العميل 2] على ركبتيك، فاسق! -[العميل 3] على ركبتيك!
-[Geonyoung shouting] -[Yejin screams]
-[صراخ جيونيونج] -[صرخات يجين]
-Open the door! -[door knob rattling]
-افتح الباب! -[طقطقة مقبض الباب]
Hey, you bastard!
مهلا، أيها الوغد!
[investigators groaning in pain]
[المحققون يئنون من الألم]
[Yejin shouting]
[يصرخ يجين]
[Geonyoung] Open the fucking door!
[Geonyoung] افتح الباب اللعين!
[door thudding under kicks]
[ارتطام الباب تحت الركلات]
[investigators clamoring]
[صراخ المحققين]
[door opens]
[يفتح الباب]
[agent] All clear, sir.
[الوكيل] كل شيء واضح يا سيدي.
[groans softly]
[آهات بهدوء]
[Geonyoung] Open the door! Hey, open the door!
[جيونيونج] افتح الباب! مهلا، افتح الباب!
[investigators clamoring]
[صراخ المحققين]
[Geonyoung] Get the tear gas!
[Geonyoung] احصل على الغاز المسيل للدموع!
[agents shouting]
[صراخ العملاء]
[agent] Head on the ground, asshole!
[العميل] ضع رأسك على الأرض، أيها الأحمق!
Hey!
يا!
[Geonyoung] Hey, the tear gas!
[Geonyoung] مهلا، الغاز المسيل للدموع!
Shit, it's hot!
اللعنة، الجو حار!
It's hot!
الطقس حار!
Move!
يتحرك!
[Gukpyeong sighs]
[غوكبيونغ يتنهد]
[Gukpyeong] Do you not realize how serious this is?
[غوكبيونغ] ألا تدركين مدى خطورة الأمر؟
The Japanese Metropolitan Police Department
قسم شرطة العاصمة اليابانية
put those Yakuza bastards on the wanted list.
ضع هؤلاء الأوغاد في ياكوزا على قائمة المطلوبين.
They even sent over a formal request for cooperation, Mr. Jo.
حتى أنهم أرسلوا طلبًا رسميًا للتعاون يا سيد جو.
[Daeil] Sir, I'm really sorry we didn't clear it with you first.
[دائيل] سيدي، أنا آسف حقًا لأننا لم نوضح الأمر معك أولاً.
But still, after everything we've paid up until now,
ولكن لا يزال، بعد كل ما دفعناه حتى الآن،
isn't this the time you step in and cover us?
أليس هذا هو الوقت المناسب لتتدخل وتغطينا؟
[Gukpyeong] Who the hell is this guy?
[غوكبيونغ] من هو هذا الرجل بحق الجحيم؟
[Manjae] Sir, please forgive him.
[مانجاي] سيدي، يرجى أن يغفر له.
This guy doesn't… He doesn't know any better.
هذا الرجل لا... إنه لا يعرف أفضل من ذلك.
[Daeil] It won't happen again.
[دائيل] لن يحدث ذلك مرة أخرى.
We just got a little greedy and messed up.
لقد حصلنا على القليل من الجشع والفوضى.
If you help us out just this once, we'll make sure to pay you back for it!
إذا ساعدتنا هذه المرة فقط، فسنتأكد من سداد ثمن ذلك لك!
[Gukpyeong] Wow. This one's got more guts than him, right?
[غوكبيونغ] واو. هذا الشخص لديه شجاعة أكثر منه، أليس كذلك؟
Hey, you're better.
مهلا، أنت أفضل.
[Manjae] Yeah, you're right.
[مانجاي] نعم، أنت على حق.
He's got guts. If you'd forgive us just this once…
لديه الشجاعة. لو سامحتنا هذه المرة فقط...
[Manjae spluttering]
[مانجاي يرتجف]
[Gukpyeong] Shut it. [clicks tongue]
[جوكبيونج] اصمت. [نقرات اللسان]
[breathing shakily]
[تتنفس بشكل مرتعش]
[Kitae] Sir, it's probably best to leave him.
[كيتاي] سيدي، ربما يكون من الأفضل تركه.
We'll need someone to pull the gang back together as their new leader.
سنحتاج إلى شخص ما ليجمع العصابة معًا كزعيم جديد لهم.
The election's right around the corner.
الانتخابات على الأبواب.
[Daeil breathing shakily]
[دايل يتنفس مرتعشا]
You think you can do well?
هل تعتقد أنه يمكنك القيام بعمل جيد؟
Yes, sir.
نعم يا سيدي.
Yeah?
نعم؟
[Gukpyeong sighs]
[غوكبيونغ يتنهد]
[agent 1] On your knees!
[العامل 1] على ركبتيك!
-[agent 2] Stay still! -[agent 1] Stop resisting!
-[العميل 2] ابق ساكنًا! -[العميل 1] توقف عن المقاومة!
[sighs]
[تنهدات]
Who the hell screwed us over and snatched Jo Manjae?
من الذي خدعنا بحق الجحيم وخطف جو مانجاي؟
[door swings open]
[يتأرجح الباب مفتوحا]
-Hello. So… -[Yejin] Morning, sir.
-مرحبًا. إذن... -[يجين] صباح الخير يا سيدي.
-[door closes] -Did you guys clean the office yet?
-[الباب يُغلق] -هل قمتم يا رفاق بتنظيف المكتب بعد؟
-[Yejin] Clean? -[Investigator Kim] No, we didn't…
-[يجين] نظيف؟ -[المحقق كيم] لا، لم نفعل...
[Geonyoung] How many times have I told you to clean up?
[Geonyoung] كم مرة طلبت منك التنظيف؟
Just look at this place!
مجرد إلقاء نظرة على هذا المكان!
-[Yejin] I'm sorry, sir. -[Geonyoung] Huh?
-[يجين] أنا آسف يا سيدي. -[جيونيونج] هاه؟
[Investigator Kim] Ms. Oh, go and… Go get the broom and the dustpan.
[المحقق كيم] السيدة أوه، اذهبي و... اذهبي وأحضري المكنسة والمجرفة.
[Yejin] Yes, sir. I'll bring the dustpan and sweep up.
[يجين] نعم يا سيدي. سأحضر مجرود وأكنس.
And these useless boxes. Get them all out to the storage room!
وهذه الصناديق عديمة الفائدة. أخرجهم جميعًا إلى غرفة التخزين!
[Investigator Kim] Okay, I'll clear them out.
[المحقق كيم] حسنًا، سأقوم بإخلاء سبيلهم.
[Geonyoung] And what the hell is this bag doing here, huh?
[Geonyoung] وماذا تفعل هذه الحقيبة هنا بحق الجحيم، هاه؟
Why would you leave a bag lying around here?
لماذا تترك حقيبة ملقاة هنا؟
-[Yejin] I'm sorry. -[Investigator Kim] I'll put it away.
-[يجين] أنا آسف. -[المحقق كيم] سأضعه جانبًا.
-[♪ gripping music plays] -[bug detector beeping]
-[♪ تشغيل الموسيقى الرائعة] -[صفير كاشف الأخطاء]
Lay low for a while.
استلقي منخفضًا لفترة من الوقت.
You don't have to give me all this.
ليس عليك أن تعطيني كل هذا.
I won't breathe a word to Director Hwang.
لن أتحدث بكلمة واحدة إلى المدير هوانج.
Don't worry, sir.
لا تقلق يا سيدي.
If I was worried about you running your mouth,
إذا كنت قلقة بشأن تشغيل فمك،
I would've let you die back there.
كنت سأتركك تموت هناك.
Then why did you…
ثم لماذا…
[Kitae] I told you.
[كيتاي] قلت لك.
You're Jo Manjae's replacement now.
أنت بديل جو مانجاي الآن.
The whole gang's already in pieces,
العصابة بأكملها مقسمة بالفعل،
so why would you even need a replacement?
فلماذا تحتاج حتى إلى بديل؟
The business.
العمل.
You've got to keep it going, don't you?
عليك أن تستمر في الأمر، أليس كذلك؟
[Geonyoung] All right, open up the cabinet and toss out all those old files!
[Geonyoung] حسنًا، افتح الخزانة وتخلص من كل تلك الملفات القديمة!
[Yejin] Yes, sir. I will.
[يجين] نعم يا سيدي. أنا سوف.
[Investigator Kim] How many times have I told you to clean that out?
[المحقق كيم] كم مرة طلبت منك تنظيف ذلك؟
-[Yejin] I'm sorry. -[bug detector beeping]
-[يجين] أنا آسف. -[صفير كاشف الأخطاء]
[Geonyoung] And this box!
[جيونيونج] وهذا الصندوق!
-[Yejin] That's… -[Geonyoung] I told you a hundred times
-[Yejin] هذا... -[Geonyoung] أخبرتك مائة مرة
-to throw it out already! Geez! -[Yejin] That… I'm sorry!
- لرميها بالفعل! الجيز! -[يجين] ذلك... أنا آسف!
[Investigator Kim] Mr. Jang, please just leave it. We'll take care of it.
[المحقق كيم] سيد جانغ، من فضلك اترك الأمر. سوف نعتني بالأمر.
Just leave it. We'll do it.
فقط اتركه. سنفعل ذلك.
[bug detector beeping]
[صفير كاشف الأخطاء]
Me?
أنا؟
You.
أنت.
Me.
أنا.
-Us. -[sighs]
-نحن. -[تنهدات]
That meth business of yours.
أعمالك المتعلقة بالميثامفيتامين تلك.
I've had my eye on it for a long time.
لقد وضعت عيني عليها لفترة طويلة.
[Manjae] Mr. Baek, I heard
[مانجاي] السيد بايك، سمعت
you'll be going to Japan soon.
سوف تذهب إلى اليابان قريبا.
Would it be all right
هل سيكون كل شيء على ما يرام
if I asked you a small favor on your way?
إذا طلبت منك خدمة صغيرة في طريقك؟
[Kitae] That's why I did you guys the favor.
[كيتاي] لهذا السبب قدمت لكم معروفًا يا رفاق.
I'll figure out a way to reopen the connection with the Japanese.
سأكتشف طريقة لإعادة فتح الاتصال مع اليابانيين.
In the meantime,
في هذه الأثناء،
you take that money, pull the guys back together,
خذ هذا المال، واجمع الرجال معًا مرة أخرى،
and get the lab running again.
وتشغيل المختبر مرة أخرى.
You want to sell the drugs yourself?
هل تريد بيع المخدرات بنفسك؟
But…
لكن…
A government man dealing drugs…
رجل حكومي يتاجر بالمخدرات..
What?
ماذا؟
Is that a problem?
هل هذه مشكلة؟
No, sir.
لا يا سيدي.
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
[Geonyoung] I thought they were just petty thieves,
[Geonyoung] اعتقدت أنهم كانوا مجرد لصوص تافهين،
but turns out those bastards are a lot more audacious than I expected.
لكن تبين أن هؤلاء الأوغاد أكثر جرأة مما توقعت.
[Kitae] I'm Baek Kitae, KCIA Busan branch.
[كاتي] أنا أستمتع كيت، كي سي آي بوسن.
-[♪ sinister music playing] -[Geonyoung] Mr. Baek Kitae.
-[♪ عزف موسيقى شريرة] -[Geonyoung] السيد بايك كيتاي.
Looks like we'll be seeing a lot of each other from now on.
يبدو أننا سنرى الكثير من بعضنا البعض من الآن فصاعدا.
[bug detector beeping]
[صفير كاشف الأخطاء]
[laughing]
[يضحك]
All right, that's enough cleaning!
حسنًا، هذا يكفي للتنظيف!
Let's get to work!
هيا بنا إلى العمل!
[Geonyoung's laughter echoes]
[تردد صدى ضحكة جيونيونج]
Translated by Yoonjung Song
تمت الترجمة بواسطة يونجونج سونج